A Guide to the Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1979-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1979-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/1/2.871
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1987 June 5.
Contents List
- Vice President for Administration-General 1982-1984 (Box 1)
- Vice President for Administration-Planning and Budget Letter 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Vice President for Administration-Tour of Facilities on 11/04/83 1983 (Box 1)
- Vice President for Administration-Staff Meeting 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Assistant Vice President for Administration 1982-1984 (Box 1)
- Assistant Vice President for Budget and Planning 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Assistant Vice President for Budget and Planning-Sandridge File 1982-1985 (Box 1)
- Assistant Vice President for Business Operations 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Assistant Vice President for Finance 1982 (Box 1)
- Assistant Vice President for Physical Plant 1982-1984 (Box 1)
- Academic Space 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Administrative Computing-Positions Regrade 1984 (Box 1)
- Administrative Coordinators 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Advisory Boards 1982 (Box 1)
- Afro-American Affairs 1982 (Box 1)
- Alexandria Management Corporation (12/12/83) 1983 (Box 2)
- Alumni Association 1982 (Box 2)
- American Association of Higher Education 1983 (Box 2)
- Architectural and Engineering Services 1982-1984 (Box 2)
- Attorney General's Law Conference 1983 (Box 2)
- Audit of Public Accounts 1982-1983 (Box 2)
- Board of Visitors Meetings (5 folders) 1983 Oct-1984 Jun (Box 2)
- Budget Office 1983-1984 (Box 2)
- Budget Office-Financing equipment 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Budget Office-General Funds Revenue Use Summary 1983 (Box 3)
- Budget Office-Governor's Reserve 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Budget Office-Policy on Sale of Institutional Forms 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Capital Fund Drive 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Capital Outlay Forms 1981-1982 (Box 3)
- Capital Outlay Projects 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Center for the Study of Higher Education-Seminar on Planning 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Center for the Study of Higher Education-Summer Workshops 1984 (Box 3)
- Centralization Proposals n.d. (Box 3)
- Charlottesville-City Council 1982-1984 (Box 3)
- Charlottesville-Planning Bodies Quarterly Meeting 1983 (Box 3)
- Charlottesville-Community Development Office 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Charlottesville-Thomas Jefferson Planning District Comm. (empty) n.d. (Box 3)
- Charlottesville/Albemarle Employment and Training Commission 1983 (Box 3)
- Charlottesville/Albemarle "Leadership Charlottesville" Steering Committee 1983 (Box 3)
- Commerce School 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Commerce School-Annual Report 1982-1984 (Box 3)
- Commerce School-Marketing Group n.d. (Box 3)
- Commerce School-Marketing Retreat 1983 (Box 3)
- Communications Services 1982-1984 (Box 3)
- Computing Office 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Computing Office-Audit Report 1983/1984 1983 (Box 3)
- Computing Office-Statement of Policy on Computers and Telecommunications n.d. (Box 4)
- Computing and Communications-Advisory Board 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- Computing and Communications-Telephone Problems 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- Continuing Education 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- Council of Academic Deans 1982-1984 (Box 4)
- Dean of Students Office 1984 (Box 4)
- Employment Training Commission-Virginia Employment Commission Committee 1984 (Box 4)
- Equal Opportunity Programs-General 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- Equal Opportunity Programs-Advisory Committee 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- Equal Opportunity Programs-Affirmative Action Plan for Equal Employment Opportunity 1983 (Box 4)
- Equal Opportunity Programs-1982 Virginia Plan Employment Assessment 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- Executive Agreements 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- Facilities Planning Conference (Lexington, Kentucky) 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- Faculty of Arts and Sciences Meeting 1984 (Box 4)
- Food Service Division 1982-1984 (Box 4)
- General Services 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- General Services-Attorney's Fees 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- Governmental Relations 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1984 (Box 4)
- Grievance File-General 1979-1980, 1984 (Box 4)
- Handicapped Access 1981-1983 (Box 4)
- Health and Safety 1982-1984 (Box 4)
- House Appropriations Committee 1982 (Box 5)
- Housing Division 1982 (Box 5)
- Institutional Planning and Studies 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- Legal Advisor's Office 1982-1984 (Box 5)
- Legislative Matters, ad hoc Committee on 1983 (Box 5)
- Legislative Relations 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- Madison Hall Relocation 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- Maintenance of Public Facilities Report 1983 (Box 5)
- Materiel Management 1982-1984 (Box 5)
- Materiel Management-Audit 1982 (Box 5)
- Materiel Management-Procurement Problems 1983 (Box 5)
- Medical Center-Director's Office 1982-1984 (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- Neighborhood Associations 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- 911 Emergency System 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- 911 Task Force-Joint Dispatch Center 1980-1984 (Box 5)
- Personnel 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- Personnel Administration-Annual Service Awards Program 1984 (Box 5)
- Physical Plant 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- Physical Plant-Bayly Museum Landscaping 1983 (Box 6)
- Physical Plant-Grass on Lawn 1982-1984 (Box 6)
- Physical Plant-Historic Landmarks (Morea and Faulkner House) 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- Physical Plant-Internal Audit 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- Physical Plant-Painter Problem 1984 (Box 6)
- Police Department 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- Police Department-Audit Report 1984 (Box 6)
- Police Department-Tailgating Meeting 1983 (Box 6)
- President's Office 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- President's Office-City, County and University Luncheon Meeting 1983 (Box 6)
- President's Office-Commencement Exercises 1984 May (Box 6)
- President's Office-Commonwealth Day 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- President's Office-Control of the University 1980 (Box 6)
- President's Office-Fall Convocation 1983 (Box 6)
- President's Office-Founder's Day 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- President's Office-Lawn Society Dinner 1983 (Box 6)
- President's Office-Parents Day Weekend 1983 (Box 6)
- President's Office-President Retreat 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- President's Office-Reception for 1st Year Students 1983 (Box 6)
- Printing and Mail Service 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Printing Office-Standardization Proposals n.d. (Box 7)
- Provost's Office 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Real Estate 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Real Estate-Blandy Farm 1982-1983 (Box 7)
- Real Estate-Roanoke Property 1983 (Box 7)
- Research Faculty Forum 1983 (Box 7)
- Residential Housing 1982-1984 (Box 7)
- Risk Management 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Risk Management-Director and Officers Alumni Board of Trustees 1982 (Box 7)
- Risk Management-Insurance Cancellation 1983 (Box 7)
- Risk Management-Liability Insurance 1982-1984 (Box 7)
- Risk Management-Property Insurance 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Risk Management-School Board Liability Insurance 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Risk Management-State Program 1982-1984 (Box 7)
- Risk Management-Task Force Committee (White Paper) 1983 (Box 7)
- Risk Management-Worker's Compensation 1982-1984 (Box 7)
- Risk Management and Safety-Fire Safety (Robert Carter) 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- Science and Technology Task Force 1982 (Box 8)
- SCT Corporation 1983 (Box 8)
- State Council of Higher Education 1982-1984 (Box 8)
- State Department of Budget and Planning 1982, 1984 (Box 8)
- State Department of General Services 1982-1983 (Box 8)
- State House Appropriations Committee 1982-1983 (Box 8)
- State Legislature 1983 1982-1983 (Box 8)
- State Mineral Management Plan 1982 (Box 8)
- State Secretary of Education 1982, 1984 (Box 8)
- State Publications 1982 (Box 8)
- State-Wide Statistics 1983 (Box 8)
- Student Affairs 1982-1984 (Box 8)
- Student Papers 1982 (Box 8)
- Summer Session 1984 (Box 8)
- Supervisory Development Program Speech 1984 (Box 8)
- Support Services 1982 (Box 8)
- SURA Linear Accelerator Sites 1983 (Box 8)
- Telecommunications Department (Richmond) 1982, 1984 (Box 8)
- United Way-J. H. King 1983-1984 (Box 8)
- University Relations 1982-1984 (Box 9)
- Vice President and Provost 1982-1984 (Box 9)
- Associate Provost for Research 1983-1984 (Box 9)
- Vice President for Business and Fince 1982-1984 (Box 9)
- Vice President for Development and University Relations 1982-1984 (Box 9)
- Vice President for Health Affairs 1982 (Box 9)
- Vice President for Student Affairs 1982-1983 (Box 9)
- Vice President for Administration Workshop 1983-1984 (Box 9)
- Virginia Plan for Higher Education 1982, 1984 (Box 9)
- Virginia Register Act 1982 (Box 9)